

Personal Statement

I have always been keen on making and learning things. In programming, I found a way to explore this passion. I'm very interested in Web Development, especially front-end and I'm looking forward to gain new skills and experience in the field.

Contact Details

- ♀ Porto, Portugal
- hello@dev-pedrobrandao.com
- in apedrobrn
- apedrobrnpnq
- www.dev-pedrobrandao.com

Skills

Team Work
Attention to Detail
Problem Solving
Quick Learning

Pedro Brandão

Professional Experience FREELANCE WEB DEVELOPER

Oct. 2021- Present

- Developed a portfolio for an artist Custom website developed using NextJS and Prismic as a CMS. (inespinheiro.vercel.app)
- Developed a web app for a company
 Web Application developed with NextJS and
 Prismic as a CMS. Also has built-in
 authentication. (www.aasm-furniture.com)

FRONT-END DEVELOPMENT INTERN @ SMARTEX

Mar 2021- Jul. 2021

 Worked on a dashboard developed with React connected to a NodeJS Backend
 Added new functionalities to make CRUD operations, implemented automatic daily and weekly reports sent by email, and new graphs to analyze system performance.

Education

INSTITUTO SUPERIOR DE ENGENHARIA DO PORTO Sept. 2018 - Sept. 2021

Bachelor's degree in Informatics Engineering

- Average of 14/20
- Developed a SPA using Angular for OPT Transport Optimization and Planning
- Developed a Factory Floor Management Software with Java and C
- Developed a Ride Sharing software using Java

Other Relevant Experience

MASTER CLASS ON DATA VISUALIZATION

aPorto Business School

MASTER CLASS ON CREATIVE COMPUTING BIO-INSPIRED IN ARTIFICAL INTELIGENCE

Online Lecture organised by ISEP

IT & Languages

- Software Development (NextJS, React, JavaScript, Node.js, Python, Java)
- GIT
- Terminal Usage
- Photoshop
- Proficient in English
- Native Portuguese Speaker